ourpatch.com.au 2009-10-01

# Privacy Policy | Australia | OurPatch

## We are committed to your privacy

 **REGIONAL MEDIA NETWORKS PTY LIMITED  
ABN 73 127 723 755  
PRIVACY POLICY**

Regional Media Networks Pty Limited (OurPatch) respects the privacy of individuals. This policy sets out how Ourpatch collects personal information on, from and in respect of the operation of www.ourpatch.com.au (OurPatch Website). It also describes how OurPatch maintains, uses and discloses personal information and your rights of access and correction.

If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please contact our OurPatch Customer Service: 

Email: [info@ourpatch.com.au](mailto:customerservice@ourpatch.com.au)

Phone: 1300-OurPatch or 0282565888

Post: Customer Service, OurPatch,  Box 103, 272 Victoria Avenue, Chatswood, NSW, 2067

 **1.  What personal information does OurPatch collect?**

1.1 General  
OurPatch collects personal information for its business purposes, which are generally detailed on the OurPatch Website.

1.2 Information gathered by website technology  
1.2.1 The OurPatch Website may use cookies or other technology to make a record of your visit and log your information for statistical and business purposes. Such information includes your server address, domain name, IP address, the date and time of your visit, pages accessed, documents downloaded, previous website visited and the type of browser used. The data collected from cookies helps us to analyse browsing patterns of users in order to improve the content and design of the OurPatch Website and helps us serve you each time you return.  
1.2.2 If you do not wish information to be gathered on a cookie it is possible to disable the acceptance of cookies by your web browser. If you want to do this and are not sure  how you should contact your ISP.  However, this may affect our ability to track your orders or to recognise you as a registered advertiser, which allows you to access  your account information.  
1.2.3 The aggregated statistical information collected from cookies technology may be shared with our partners to help them understand how the community uses the site.  Such information does not include your personal data.

1.3 email   
If you send us an email message we will record your email address. We will only use your email address for the purpose for which it was provided (for example, responding to a query). We will not use your email address for any other purposes (including adding it to any mailing list) without your express approval.

1.4 Referrals  
1.4.1 You may have the option to use “send to a friend” links about particular products, events or other material on the website. We will only use your friend’s name and email address for the particular purpose for which it was provided by you.  
1.4.2 We will not use your friend’s email address for any other purposes (including adding it to any mailing list) without their express approval.  
1.4.3 You or your friend may contact us to remove respective names and emails from our records by contacting Customer Service.

1.5 Forms  
If we require you to complete an electronic form on the OurPatch Website and, in doing so, it requires you to enter personal information (eg. Registration Form), we will collect that information to allow us to perform the service or provide the facility described. We may also use that information to send you information about our products,  services and promotions. However, you may opt out of receiving marketing information or contact from us by contacting Customer Service. We will not collect personal information that would be unlawful, unnecessary or unrelated to OurPatch’s business.

1.6 Advertisers  
1.6.1 If you wish to purchase advertising on the OurPatch Website, you must provide us with certain personal information to allow us to process and/or confirm your details, order and payment.  
1.6.2 We keep a record of your purchase data for our reporting and accounting purposes. This data may be used for marketing to you by OurPatch. However, if you do not wish to receive such information, please contact us at Customer Service. At no time will your credit card details be released to a third party.    
1.6.3 OurPatch uses Internet Payment Gateway to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card transactions over the Internet. Confidential information including client credit card details are encrypted the moment they are transmitted from the client’s browser to the banking network using industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology )128-bit RC4 encryption technology.  
1.6.4 A client’s credit card details are not stored anywhere on the Internet and the only company who has access to this data is the merchant’s bank. The bank also sends confirmation information via the same encryption technology back to the client’s browser. These secure processes provide clients with peace of mind when purchasing online.  
1.6.5 If your browser or firewall doesn’t support SSL, you will not be able to connect to the server, which means you won’t be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please place your order by phone at 1300 OurPatch or 02 82655888

2. Use 

2.1 Restriction  
Personal information that you supply to OurPatch will only be used for the purposes for which you have provided it and to assist us to conduct our business.   
2.2 Consent  
We may from time to time send you invitations to, or information about, events, competitions, promotions, products or services. We will not send you any of these communications if you have informed us that you do not wish to receive them. If you do not wish to receive such information, please contact us at Customer Service.

3. Disclosure  
3.1 Personal information  
3.1.1 OurPatch will not disclose your personal information to a third party except in accordance with this privacy policy. OurPatch may from time to time use external service providers or agents who may have access to some personal information we collect. We will use our best endeavours to ensure that these third parties may only access information to the extent necessary for the services OurPatch requires (for example marketing communications or managing databases) and that such providers will be bound by the same standard of confidentiality as contained in this policy.  
3.1.2 Any personal information provided to us is not sold to third party data compilation services.  
3.2 Other website links  
If the OurPatch Website contains a link to another website, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. In particular, if you chose to utilise the del.icio.us or Digg it functions available to you on the site, you should be aware that all activity run through these sites is managed their own separate policies.   
3.3 Security  
OurPatch takes reasonable measures to keep all personal information secure against loss, unauthorised access, modification, disclosure or other misuse.  
3.4 Access  
You may request access to the personal information we hold about you or seek correction of it by contacting Customer Service.
